(bright music)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(wind blowing)
(leaves rustling)
(suspenseful music)
(wind blowing) (leaves rustling)
(lock clangs) (pages rustling)
[Narrator] A forest.
Now. for many of us. the forest
represents different things.
It may be a magical place.
a place of adventure.
It may be a place of play.
It may also be a place of fear.
(gunshot blasts)
(wings fluttering)
(birds chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot blasts) (bullet thuds)
A place of hungry wolves
or conniving witches.
A place where children
go and never return.
But it may also be a home.
a place where families are born.
(peaceful music)
(leaves rustling)
(peaceful music continues)
Where they grow.
where they prosper.
where a parent teaches its
child the ways of the world.
which. of course.
includes its dangers.
(suspenseful music)
Because it's a parent's
intuition. isn't it?
To protect no matter the cost.
(suspenseful music continues)
'Cause sometimes. no
matter how hard you try
to shield yourself
and your family
from the dangers of a world.
(spade thuds)
Sometimes life has other ideas.
(suspenseful music continues)
Because there comes
a time in every life
when its world is
changed forever.
For the life affected.
the question then becomes.
how does it cope?
Or maybe they become
angry. bitter. twisted.
hellbent on revenge.
Because what happens
if the forest fights back?
(dramatic music)
(gunshot blasts)
You ever shot a deer?
No. Have you?
Yeah. Once.
(suspenseful music)
(bird thuds)
So you're not coming?
Do you know what. Simon?
I'm gonna tell him. I am.
Because after everything
you've said to him.
everything you promised.
you just can't be bothered.
You wan to be pretend
to be on a work trip.
You know what else? Fuck you.
Fuck you.
(dramatic gaming music)
You're gonna be sick if
you play that in the car.
(dramatic gaming
music continues)
Benji? Benji. come on.
(melancholic music)
(suspenseful music)
Come on. Bloody
thing. (fist thudding)
Off anywhere nice. are we?
Yeah. We're visiting
his dad's family.
Oh. (chuckles) Family's hey?
The only thing worse than
your own is someone else's.
You can choose your partners.
but you can't choose
your in-laws. am I right?
Mine are a nightmare.
Getting (indistinct). I think
is the best thing I can.
(Rob gasps) (brakes screeching)
Sorry about that. love.
They've been tearing around
these roads there for weeks.
But they're up to something
though. You mark my words.
Something criminal.
(Benji's stomach rumbling)
Friend of mine. the other night.
he got driven into
a ditch. he did.
Car's completely right off.
So we got off lightly.
if anything. (chuckles)
Excuse me? Can you pull over?
-Oh. oh. Yeah. sure.
-Please?
-Yeah.
-He's gonna be sick.
[Rob] Alright. Okay.
(gravel crunching)
Go. go. go. go.
(Benji retching)
Get it up.
Get it up. get it
all up. That's it.
And again.
(Benji spitting)
Better? Come on. sit
down for a minute. okay.
Give it a minute here.
You okay? You might wanna
listen to me in the future.
Thought Dad was picking me up.
Yeah. Well. he got delayed.
What happened?
Nothing. Just a work thing.
You're getting
deported. aren't you?
What?
Deported. You and dad
not married anymore.
No. Benji. No. we're
not getting deported.
Come on. He's gonna meet
us at your grandma's.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah. so come
on. get in the cab.
(Bambi growling)
Benji. come on.
(door thuds)
(dramatic rumbling)
He's just like what my
little boy used to be like.
Less than five
minutes down the road
and he'd be spewing up his guts.
And then the cheeky
get to blame me for it.
Hey. sucking on a sweet.
that's what used to take
his mind off things.
Cheeky little bugger.
(Bambi growling)
(hooves thudding)
(metal clanging)
(Xana shouting and groaning)
(metal creaking)
(Xana coughing)
Benji.
Is everybody all right?
Is everyone okay?
(Xana coughing)
(hooves thudding)(leaves
rustling)
(Xana breathing heavily)
I think it's still out there.
(Bambi growls)
(metal clanging)
(Rob moaning and groaning)
Oh. Oh.
That's okay.
What's going on. Mom?
Oh. thank God.
(metal clanging)
(Rob screaming)
Mom. there's something wet.
(Rob screaming continues)
(metal clanging continues)
(bones crunching)
You're gonna move back.
Move back behind me.
Keep your eyes closed.
(Rob screaming) (metal clanging)
Move to the front.
(metal clanging)
(glass shattering)
(Xana groaning)
(metal clanging)
(suspenseful music)
(Bambi growling)
Move.
(suspenseful music)
(creepy music)
Bambi.
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
Benji. come on. Come on.
Bambi.
(oven timer ringing)
(meat squishing)
Trust her to make us
go and wait like this.
Well. you know what
the taxis are like.
especially around here.
Andrew. (fingers
clicking) Kitchen roll.
[Josh] Isn't Simon
picking them up?
Simon? Simon's not coming.
Our brother has a
work do. Apparently.
At least he had the
decency to let us know.
Well. why don't you
give her a call?
I would do. but I don't
have any signal here. do I?
[Josh] Um? Landline?
Had to have it disconnected.
Why?
[Andrew] Mother kept
calling the police.
[Mary] Your mother.
(suspenseful music)
Mary?
[Mary] Bambi.
Mary. Come back inside. please.
Oh. Or speak.
(footsteps squelching)
It's hard enough being
married to your son
without you running off.
I thought I told you to
watch her. Sit there.
I was.
Just don't let her
out of your sight.
Well. actually. you're
not my real mum.
You'll get fat. you know?
If you keep eating those.
Will I?
Yeah. You'll balloon
like a bouncy castle.
Bounce. bouncy. bounce.
(both imitating laughing)
(suspenseful music)
They're here.
What was that?
Thanks. Grandma. That's
not freaky at all.
(door slams)
(Xana breathing heavily)
(finger tapping)
(engine rumbling)
(cellphone ringing)
Yeah. we're on our way back now.
Everything on track?
[Tyler] Don't worry. Trust me.
What?
[Boss] I've gotta go.
Call me when. (phone beeping)
What?
[Harriet] If it's really
as dangerous as you claim.
surely we'd be safer inside.
Okay. Well. what
about the driver?
We just left him.
[Harriet] Well.
that's his problem.
-Harriet. No.
-Well. it is.
No.
I'll go.
What? No.
I can try and get some
signal. Call for help.
Andrew.
I dunno. it's up to him.
Maybe it's for the best.
(palm thuds)
(door thuds)
(Benji crying)
[Benji] Ah.
(peaceful music)
(suspenseful music)
[Michael] Anything?
(suspenseful music continues)
She pretty tasty. hey?
(Bambi growls)
What was that?
Behind me.
(suspenseful music continues)
(Mary humming)
Grandma?
Grandma? (fingers
clicking) Grandma?
(suspenseful music continues)
Shut up!
[Xana] Harrison.
What?
Don't do that.
Why not?
Because it's mean.
She's annoying.
You're annoying.
(Mary humming)
(suspenseful music)
(twigs snapping)
He's dead. isn't he? The driver.
No. No. Josh was with him.
It'll be okay.
Try not to think about it. okay?
When's Dad getting here?
Soon.
He'll know what to do.
(melancholic music)
Ow.
-Sorry.
(melancholic music continues)
Sorry.
(twigs snapping)
(gunshot blasts)
(bullet thuds) (Josh groans)
(Josh thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(Xana gasps)
It's creepy. isn't it?
[Xana] What is it?
I don't know. She's been
painting them for weeks.
Brought you some clothes.
Oh. thanks.
They're Harriet's. so.
I'll be careful.
Thank you.
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful music)
Fuck. fuck. fuck.
fuck. fuck. fuck.
(Tyler breathing heavily)
(Michael breathing deeply)
[Eddie] Where'd he come from?
Another crash. do you reckon?
No. No. too clean.
Staying in that motherfucking
house is my guess.
[Eddie] What's he
doing out here?
Fuck knows.
Take him back to the truck.
(suspenseful music)
(water splashing)
(candy rattling)
(candy thuds)
Wimp.
[Harriet] Harrison!
What?
[Harriet] Come here.
please. darling.
Why?
[Harriet] Because I said so.
(Benji chuckling)
What are you laughing at?
Um.
Darling. so sad.
[Benji] What's sad. Grandma?
I don't know why you
bother. She's lost it.
She's all. (groaning)
Darling. this is Simon.
Grandma?
No. Not my son.
[Harriet] Harrison!
What?
[Harriet] I said come here.
(footsteps thudding)
Oh. Simon.
It's Benji. Grandma.
[Mary] Oh.
(suspenseful music)
(light switch clicks)
(fire crackling)
(lights clicking) (fire
crackling continues)
(pages rustling)
(wind howling)
(lights clicking)
(pages rustling)
Grandma?
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful music)
Mom! Mom!
Benji? Benji!
Benji.
Mom. it's back.
(suspenseful music)
(fire crackling)
Move! Go. go. go.
Get back. Go Benji!
(glass shattering)
(suspenseful music continues)
Go Benji!
(wood cracking) (suspenseful
music continues)
(glass shattering)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi growling)
(Harrison and Harriet screaming)
Whoa! What the fuck?
What the fuck was that?
(Bambi growling)
What the fuck?
Come. Let's go.
(Bambi growling)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Harriet screaming)
(handle squeaking)
(suspenseful music continues)
No.
(Harriet moaning)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Harriet screaming)
Come on. Mary.
(suspenseful music continues)
Mary. Go.
[Andrew] Come on.
(engine sputtering)
(suspenseful music continues)
Come on.
Wait. Where's Harriet?
(suspenseful music continues)
Where's Harriet?
Did you see her?
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi growling)
(antler squelching)
(suspenseful music continues)
(torso thuds)
(keys jangling)
(engine revving)
(suspenseful music continues)
He's coming. Dad!
Dad!
(Mary humming)
Shut the fuck up!
(suspenseful music continues)
Mom?
Go. go. go.
(hooves thudding)
(suspenseful music continues)
(brakes squealing)
(Andrew speaks indistinctly)
Shit. Stay there.
(suspenseful music continues)
Come on!
(engine roaring)
Hold on. watch
out. Bad shoulder.
(suspenseful music)
Mom!
(suspenseful music continues)
Faster. Go faster!
Come on.
Fucking put your foot down.
Gear stick's stuck.
(suspenseful music continues)
Fucking hell! Come on!
(Xana speaks indistinctly)
(Andrew speaks indistinctly)
(engine revving)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Xana breathing heavily)
(Andrew sighs)
(suspenseful music)
(bugs chirping)
(footsteps crunching)
(footsteps thudding)
(footsteps thudding continues)
(suspenseful music)
Do you think it's supposed
to be the creature?
(suspenseful music continues)
What? Was she there?
[Tyler] You're gonna
wanna see this.
(suspenseful music continues)
(Harriet gasping)
Should I?
(suspenseful music continues)
Shh.
(blood gushing)
(Harriet choking)
(blood burbling)
(suspenseful music continues)
(engine idling)
Fuck! Fucking fuck.
Are you not seeing
what I'm seeing?
There's a tree. a
massive fucking tree
in the middle of the road.
And it's all Simon's fault.
insisting that we all come down
just because he didn't
wanna spend a weekend alone
with his fucking kid.
And then what happened? The
bastard didn't even show up.
(engine idling continues)
(peaceful music)
Oh. Simon?
(peaceful music continues)
You're Simon.
It's Benji. Grandma.
Oh. Anyway.
Where is he? Where's Dad?
Simon.
he's out playing in the park.
He'll be home soon for his tea.
(peaceful music continues)
Hmm.
(suspenseful music)
Can't you just do it?
No.
-Why?
-Because they need my help.
Can't Grandma just do it?
No. Grandma.
Benji. I want you to do it.
For me. Please.
Oh. no.
Right. So when we're ready.
You gimme the signal to drive.
Exactly. Then?
Don't know.
-You do.
-I don't.
I've just explained this to
you. It's not rocket science.
I don't understand
why I have to do-
'Cause I've asked you to.
and I need you to. Okay?
(Xana sighs)
(Bambi growling)
(suspenseful music)
(hooves thudding)
Drive. Benji! Drive!
(tires squealing)
(suspenseful music continues)
Dad! Dad! (Andrew screaming)
Mom. I don't know
what to do. Mom!
(Andrew screaming continues)
Mom. Mom.
-Hold on!
(suspenseful music continues)
(Harrison crying)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi sniffing)
(branch cracks)
(Bambi growls)
(hooves thudding)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Harrison thuds)
(Harrison sniffs)
(Harrison retching)
(Bambi growling)
(fawn bleating)
(flies buzzing)
(Harrison sighs) (fawn bleating)
(hooves thudding)
Oh. (indistinct).
(engine rumbling)
(engine sputtering)
Watch your grandma.
(door thuds)
Andrew?
(flesh squelches)
(suspenseful music)
What are you?
Is he okay?
Why aren't you watching
Grandma? Where is she?
Grandma? Grandma?
No. no. Shh. shh.
Okay.
She's there.
(suspenseful music)
Come on.
(footsteps thudding)
(Harrison gagging)
Oh. for fuck's sake. (crying)
(branch cracks)
(leaves rustling)
(paws thudding)
(rabbit chirruping)
What the fuck do you want?
(foot thuds)
You fucking thing.
(suspenseful music)
(rabbit squealing)
No.
(rabbits chirruping)
(suspenseful music)
Sorry.
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(metal clangs)
(Harrison screaming)
(material tearing)
(flesh squelching)
(Harrison screaming continues)
(suspenseful music continues)
(leaves rustling)
-What's that smell?
-Shh.
(Mary humming)
Stay here. okay?
-But.
Benji. I mean it. Stay here.
(Mary mumbling)
Mary? Mary. it's me. Xana.
(suspenseful music)
Mary?
Mary. it's me. Xana.
Hey. are you okay?
You gotta stay with
me and Benji. Mary.
(Mary mumbling)
It's okay. Okay?
We're worried about you.
(Mary mumbling)
Death. Death.
(flare roaring)
Benji? Benji. what the
hell are you doing?
Mom. I just thought
I saw something.
Did you not listen
to a word I said?
(flare roaring continues)
(suspenseful music)
(Xana gasps)
(flare roaring continues)
(suspenseful music)
♪ And here he comes down
to the (indistinct) ♪
♪ You better go into the skies
Mary. Mary. shh.
(Mary singing indistinctly)
(Bambi growling)
There definitely was.
(suspenseful music)
(Bambi growling)
Run!
(suspenseful music)
(footsteps thudding)
Come on. Mary. Come on.
(indistinct). it's okay.
(suspenseful music continues)
(Xana screams) (suspenseful
music continues)
It's okay. Benji. run!
(suspenseful music continues)
(engine idling)
(suspenseful music)
So there's a little
boy. Harrison. He's 15.
He's on his own. We
need to call the police.
I think it's best we get
you back to our house.
There's satellite phone there.
And there's another
guy. Josh. He's 30.
Try not to worry. love.
We'll look after you.
We'll get you back. get
you warm. call the police.
We'll work out what to do.
You'll be safe there. Promise.
(suspenseful music)
(gravel crunching)
(bird thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(Bambi growling)
(suspenseful music continues)
With me.
[Eddie] Where?
So we gonna give the
police a call now. yeah?
You okay.
-Mm.
(metal clanging)
(suspenseful music)
It's your father.
Jo?
(suspenseful music continues)
Jo. is that you?
Jo?
(suspenseful music continues)
Jo. is that you?
It's all right.
Michael. It's me.
You can lower your weapon.
I thought you might have been.
Dad? Dad.
(footsteps thudding)
Made me drive through it.
Benji.
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(footsteps thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(Tyler sighs)
(fawn bleating)
Shut the fuck up. (groans)
(suspenseful music continues)
[Xana] You better have a
fucking good explanation.
[Simon] Let's try
and not swear. Xana.
[Xana] Are you
fucking kidding me?
[Simon] Will you
please stop swearing?
[Xana] How do you know them?
How do you know those men?
(suspenseful music)
[Simon] It's complicated.
[Xana] Oh. it's complicated?
[Simon] Yes.
[Xana] Do you know what's
complicated. Simon?
Your son has just seen his
uncle dead on the road.
That's complicated.
(suspenseful music)
[Simon] Andrew?
(suspenseful music continues)
[Xana] Yes.
[Simon] And Josh?
(suspenseful music continues)
[Xana] I don't know.
I did tell you. didn't I?
I did tell you not to come.
Is that all you've got to say?
None of you were
supposed to be here.
[Xana] I wanted to
look out for Benji.
I didn't wanna let Benji down.
[Simon] Really? Really?
So that's the reason
why you begged me
to take him this weekend.
[Xana] I didn't beg you.
-"Oh. oh. please."
-It's your turn.
-"Please."
-You're his dad.
[Simon] "Please. darling.
take him off my hands."
That didn't happen.
I want you to want to
spend time with him.
I want you to want a
relationship with your own child.
(door thuds)
(foot thuds)
(Benji crying)
(melancholic music)
(fawn bleating)
(suspenseful music)
Who told them to do it?
I did. But nothing like this
has ever happened before.
You've done this before?
Willbexr have been dumping
chemicals for years.
but these were
evidently different.
- Oh my God- - We
didn't know that they-
We need to call
the police. Simon.
-No.
-Yes.
-No. Don't.
-Yes. you do. Simon.
-No.
-People have died.
Your own family have died.
Yeah. and I'll go to prison.
What will Benji think. huh?
No. think about the
impact it'll have on him
having a father in prison.
(suspenseful music continues)
I don't think it will have
any impact whatsoever.
He knows exactly what it's like
not to have a father around.
Xana. Xana.
[Jo] Yeah.
[Michael] Eddie?
Eddie. are you there?
(suspenseful music)
What do we do now?
Carry on as planned.
[Eddie] Yes. boss?
How are you getting on?
(suspenseful music continues)
We're nearly there.
[Michael] Let us know
when you're ready.
Roger that.
(fawn bleating)
(suspenseful music)
Jesus Christ.
[Tyler] Sorry.
What have you fucking
gone and done now?
It's heavy.
(cage clangs)
(fawn bleating)
Shut up. Shut up!
Gimme the phone.
(Michael chuckling)
Xana.
Give me the fucking phone.
Fucking stop.
-Simon.
-Boss.
-Fucking stop.
Simon. we need to
call the police.
(suspenseful music)
Hand it over.
(suspenseful music continues)
He might not hurt
you. but I will.
(suspenseful music continues)
So fucking give it.
(phone thuds)
Now. let's calm all
this down. shall we?
Less of the histrionics.
(suspenseful music)
What the hell is all of this?
On a little clear-up
job. aren't we. boss?
Your husband here.
Ex husband.
Needs to. how should we say it?
Cover his tracks.
Now we're laying a
little trap is all.
What sort of trap?
Plan is to draw it
out of the shadows.
Draw what?
[Michael] The creature
that attacked you.
You're bringing it here?
[Michael] It's perfectly safe.
Safe? Safe?
Xana.
You knew about this.
Our son is here.
(suspenseful music continues)
You're unbelievable.
I can't believe you. I
can't fucking believe you.
We're safe here.
Benji is safer here.
Nobody is safe here. Simon.
(Mary mumbling)
Where is Benji?
(suspenseful music continues)
(fawn bleating)
(cage clangs)
(Eddie imitates fawn bleating)
Stupid fucking
thing. (fawn bleats)
You sure this is a good idea?
What do you mean?
I don't know. I mean.
it's a bit cruel.
It's a fucking animal. mate.
It doesn't have feelings.
(cage clangs)
[Tyler] I'm going for a piss.
What?
No. Can't you wait?
[Tyler] I'm desperate.
Fuck sake.
(cage clangs) (fawn bleating)
(suspenseful music continues)
(footsteps thudding)
(Tyler sighs)
(urine trickling)
(hooves thudding)
(urine trickling continues)
(wood creaking)
(suspenseful music)
(Tyler thuds)
Mary. Mary. look at me.
[Mary] Hmm?
Where's Benji? Where did he go?
Up the hill.
What hill. Mary?
-Oh. this is pointless.
-Shut up.
To fetch a pail of water.
Okay. Mary. think. think.
Where is Benji?
One day he gather them up.
(suspenseful music)
Chair. And bleed.
Kill. kill. kill. kill
[Simon] Xana. she's lost it.
No. no. no. no. no. Mary.
Mary. look at me. look
at me. It's me. I'm Xana.
And you know Benji. You
know Benji. you love Benji.
Where is he? Where's Benji?
Would you like some
potatoes with that?
(suspenseful music)
Chop. chop. chop. chop.
-Mary.
-Chop. chop. chop.
Chop.
(suspenseful music continues)
Benji! Benji!
Xana!
Fuck. Benji!
Xana.
Shit. Benji!
Xana. come back inside.
Benji!
(suspenseful music)
[Simon] Xana!
(suspenseful music continues)
(plastic rustling)
(Xana groaning)
(suspenseful music continues)
Fuck sake.
(suspenseful music)
Tyler.
(footsteps thudding)
(flies buzzing)
(suspenseful music)
(flashlight thuds)
(Eddie retching)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi growling)
Fuck.
(suspenseful music continues)
You all right? Are you okay?
I'm gonna get you
out here. Okay?
(fawn bleating) (suspenseful
music continues)
You're safe now. (fawn bleating)
Let's get you out of here.
Eddie. come in. Eddie.
Where the fuck are they?
(suspenseful music continues)
Will one of you fucking pick up?
Boss? Boss?
(suspenseful music continues)
Fucking kid! I'm gonna kill him.
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(suspenseful music)
(door thuds)
Fuck.
(keys jangling)
(electronic beeping)
(door thuds)
(glass shattering)
(Eddie moaning)
What the fuck?
(Eddie screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(Eddie moaning) (suspenseful
music continues)
(Eddie screaming)
(suspenseful music continues)
Benji! Benji!
Mom?
[Xana] Benji!
Mom.
Mom. where are you?
[Xana] Benji!
Mom!
(suspenseful music)
Whoa! Where is he. Jo?
Jo? Jo?
(suspenseful music)
(Bambi growling)
(door creaking)
(household items thudding)
(Bambi snarling)
(Bambi sniffing)
(Bambi growling)
(door thuds) (Jo screams)
(suspenseful music)
(wood cracking) (suspenseful
music continues)
(Jo screaming) (suspenseful
Fuck you!
(flames roaring)
(house explodes)
There you are. you
little fucking shit.
[Xana] Benji!
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Just gimme a fucking
second. yeah?
[Michael] Hand it over.
Stay still. Stay still.
Hand it over.
Hey. do it. Benji. Do it.
(suspenseful music)
Do what he says.
Give me the fucking phone.
(suspenseful music continues)
Benji. give it to us!
No.
Please. Simon. Please.
This is you. this is. Turn
him against me. poison him.
Mom's got nothing to do
with it. Mom lied for you.
I heard what you said.
Enough!
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi growling)
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(gunshots blasting)
(suspenseful music continues)
[Benji] Dad!
(gunshots blasting continues)
(Michael screaming and groaning)
(suspenseful music)
-Give me.
-Thank you.
(Xana moaning) (suspenseful
music continues)
Fuck.
Give me the phone. Simon.
No.
Come on. It's over.
No. I won't let you. Xana.
I won't let you ruin my life.
Your life?
[Benji] Mom!
(suspenseful music)
Simon.
(suspenseful music continues)
Sorry. Sorry.
Mom.
(Bambi growling)
[Xana] Benji.
Mom.
Listen to me. Stay very still.
When I tell you. you are gonna
run as fast as you can. Okay?
I'm not leaving you.
I'm not like him.
You have to.
(suspenseful music continues)
I'm sorry. Benji.
I should have told
you about your dad.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
(fawn bleats) (suspenseful
music continues)
He wants his baby.
Benji. you're gonna
stay very still.
And just trust me.
(Bambi growling)
It's okay. Fawn's okay.
(suspenseful music continues)
Benji.
(Bambi growling)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Bambi growling continues)
It's okay. It's okay.
(suspenseful music continues)
(fawn bleating)
(Bambi purring) (suspenseful
music continues)
(peaceful music)
(gunshots blasting)
No!
Die. you fucking son of a bitch.
(gun hammer clicking)
(gunshot blasts)
(Michael thuds)
Grandma? Grandma?
Grandma.
Benji. Oh. my dear Benji.
(Mary crying)
(melancholic music)
(material rustling)
(gravel crunching)
(Simon breathing heavily)
(suspenseful music)
(engine idling)
(electronic beeping)
(Simon screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(Benji and Mary crying)
(Bambi purring)
(fawn bleating)
(peaceful music)
(indistinct lyrics)
♪ (indistinct) doubts it
♪ Think I don't know
how to talk about it ♪
♪ Wish sometimes that.
wish sometimes that ♪
♪ Don't know where'd
I be (indistinct) ♪
♪ Wish sometime that.
wish sometimes that ♪
(indistinct lyrics)
(peaceful music continues)
♪ I've done enough right here
♪ If you fall in love with me
(fawn bleating)
♪ I don't know where'd I be
(peaceful music continues)
♪ If you fall in love with me
(rock music) (indistinct lyrics)
♪ I don't know who I've been
♪ If you fall in love with me
♪ I don't know who I'd be
(peaceful music)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-